UNITE Publications 6000 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 1, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 11: Voice, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.57:no.4 (1995:Holiday). Copy 2.
  - Item 12: Voice, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.58:no.1 (1997:Winter)
  - Item 13: Voice, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.58:no.2 (1997:Spring)
  - Item 14: Voice, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.58:no.2 (1997:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 15: Voice, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.58:no.3 (1997:Fall)
  - Item 16: Voice, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.59:no.1 (1998:Winter)
- Box: 1, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Voice, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.60:no.1 (2001:Winter)
  - Item 2: Voice, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.60:no.1 (2001:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Voice, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.60:no.1 (2001:Winter). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Voice, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.60:no.2 (2001:Summer)
  - Item 5: Voice, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.60:no.2 (2001:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 6: Voice, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.60:no.3 (2001:Fall)
  - Item 7: Voice, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.61:no.1 (2002:Winter)
  - Item 8: Voice, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.61:no.2 (2002:Spring)
  - Item 9: Voice, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.61:no.3 (2002:Autumn)
  - Item 10: Voice, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.62:no.2 (2003:Spring)
  - Item 11: Voice, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.62:no.3 (2003:Fall)
  - Item 12: Voice, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.62:no.2 (2003:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 13: Voice, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.62:no.1 (2003:Winter)
  - Item 14: Voice, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.62:no.1 (2003:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 15: Voice, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.63:no.1 (2004:Spring)
- Box: 1, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The Magnet, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Author: NY Apparel and Allied Workers Joint Board: Local 10, Local 89-22-1, Local 155
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1998:Summer). Volume 1 not yet named.
  - Item 2: The Magnet, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1998:Summer). Volume 1 not yet named. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Magnet, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1998:Winter). Volume 1 not yet named.
  - Item 4: The Magnet, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1999:Spring)
  - Item 5: The Magnet, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (2000:Winter)
- Box: 2, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Acuerdo do Fusion y Constitucion de UNITE., Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union)
  - Item 2: Acuerdo do Fusion y Constitucion de UNITE., Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: Copy 2.
- Box: 2, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Bankrolling a Brutal Dictatorship: How Fred's Inc. Supports Burma's Military Regime Through Its Apparel Imports., Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Box: 2, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Bargaining Unit Directory., 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Box: 2, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Bargaining Unit Directory., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Box: 2, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Basic Spanish Words and Phrases For UNITE Leaders Who Don't Speak Spanish., Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Box: 2, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Beware of Extra Charges: Read about Cintas customers' bad experiences and find out how to protect your business from being ripped off., Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Beware of Extra Charges: Read about Cintas customers' bad experiences and find out how to protect your business from being ripped off., Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Beware of Extra Charges: Read about Cintas customers' bad experiences and find out how to protect your business from being ripped off., Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: Copy 3.
- Box: 2, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Cintas Exposed., Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Box: 2, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Language: French.
  - Item 6: Constitution, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: Copy2
- Box: 2, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Box: 2, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Constitutional Convention. Welcome Delegates., 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: First UNITE Constitutional Convention, Miami Beach, FL, June 28 - July 2, 1999
- Box: 2, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Consumer guide to decent clothes (including UNITE Benefits Card)., Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: Three copies of each.
- Box: 2, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Contract With Atlantic Apparel Contractors' Association, Inc., 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: June 1, 1997 - May 31 2001
  - Item 2: Contract With Atlantic Apparel Contractors' Association, Inc., 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: June 1, 1997 - May 31 2001. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Contract With Atlantic Apparel Contractors' Association, Inc., 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: June 1, 1997 - May 31 2001. Copy 3.
- Box: 2, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Delegados de UNITE: Su opinin es importante para nosotros!, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: Questionnaire. Two copies
- Box: 2, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Disability Services Council - Short staffing? Rising insurance costs? Wages that don't meet your family's needs?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Disability Services Council - Short staffing? Rising insurance costs? Wages that don't meet your family's needs?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Disability Services Council - Short staffing? Rising insurance costs? Wages that don't meet your family's needs?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Box: 2, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Disability Services Council - Why did UCP reward Pamela by reducing her hours?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Disability Services Council - Why did UCP reward Pamela by reducing her hours?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Disability Services Council - Why did UCP reward Pamela by reducing her hours?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Box: 2, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Don't let Cintas slip up when delivering your mats., Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Don't let Cintas slip up when delivering your mats., Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Box: 2, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Ergonomic Facts and Action Manual., 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Box: 2, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Ernesto Jofre Delgado: October 13, 1937 - March 5, 2001., Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Ernesto Jofre Delgado: October 13, 1937 - March 5, 2001., Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Box: 2, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Face of Change, UNITE!, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: The Face of Change, UNITE!, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: The Face of Change, UNITE!, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Box: 2, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Unite: Fighting for Our Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Welcome to Unite: Fighting for Our Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Welcome to Unite: Fighting for Our Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Box: 2, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Bienvenidos a Unite: Trabajando por Nuestro Futuro, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Seja Bem-vindo a Unite: Lutando Pelo Nosso Futuro, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Language: Portuguese.
  - Item 3: Welcome to Unite: Fighting for Our Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Language: Vietnamese.
- Box: 2, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Unite: Fighting for Our Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Language: Chinese.
  - Item 2: Welcome to Unite: Fighting for Our Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Welcome to Unite: Fighting for Our Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Box: 2, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Fightsize: Stop Sweatshops., Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Fightsize: Stop Sweatshops., Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Fightsize: Stop Sweatshops., Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Box: 2, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Fightsize: The Phony Social Security Crisis., Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Fightsize: The Phony Social Security Crisis., Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: La Talla de la Lucha: La falsa crisis del seguro social., Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: La Talla de la Lucha: La falsa crisis del seguro social., Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Box: 2, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Temas de Lucha: El embuse del Libre Comercio., Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Box: 2, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Insight, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1997:June).
  - Item 2: Insight, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1997:June). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Insight, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1997:June). Copy 3.
- Box: 2, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Insight, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1998:Oct.).
  - Item 2: Insight, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1998:Oct.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Insight, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1998:Oct.). Copy 3.
- Box: 2, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Law says you have the right to join a union, The, Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Law says you have the right to join a union, The, Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Law says you have the right to join a union, The, Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Box: 2, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: La Ley Dice Que Usted Tiene El Derecho A Ingressar En Una Union, Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Box: 2, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Life Uniform: 3 steps for Angelica corporation to improve working conditions., Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Life Uniform: 3 steps for Angelica corporation to improve working conditions., Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Life Uniform: 3 steps for Angelica corporation to improve working conditions., Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Box: 2, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Locals, Joint Boards, District Councils, Area Offices & Affiliated Organizations, 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: Part II: Local Unions Alphabetically by City & State; Local Unions Numerically Arranged.
- Box: 2, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: President Jay Mazur Is Retiring., 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Invitation
- Box: 2, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Mission Statement, Founding Convention., 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Box: 2, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Mobilizing for Power., Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Box: 2, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Moving Forward Together., 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: Day One (1995:June 23)
  - Item 2: Moving Forward Together., 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: Day Two (1995:June 24)
  - Item 3: Moving Forward Together., 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: Day Three (1995:June 26)
  - Item 4: Moving Forward Together., 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: Day Four (1995:June 27)
  - Item 5: Moving Forward Together., 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: Day Five (1995:June 28)
  - Item 6: Moving Forward Together., 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: Convention
  - Item 7: Moving Forward Together., 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Notes: Day Seven (1995:June 30)
- Box: 2, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Daily Reports to the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 21, 2003.
    Language: English; Spanish;French;Chinese.
  - Item 2: Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Daily Reports to the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 21, 2003. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Daily Reports to the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 21, 2003. Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Daily Reports to the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 22, 2003.
  - Item 5: Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Daily Reports to the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 22, 2003. Copy 2.
  - Item 6: Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Daily Reports to the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 22, 2003. Copy 3.
  - Item 7: Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Daily Reports to the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 23, 2003.
  - Item 8: Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Daily Reports to the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 23, 2003. Copy 2.
  - Item 9: Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Daily Reports to the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 23, 2003. Copy 3.
  - Item 10: Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Daily Reports to the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 24, 2003.
  - Item 11: Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Daily Reports to the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 24, 2003. Copy 2.
  - Item 12: Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Daily Reports to the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Notes: July 24, 2003. Copy 3.
- Box: 2, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Partners in Prevention: Health & Safety Action Manual for Local Unions., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: Partners in Prevention: Health & Safety Action Manual for Local Unions., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Box: 2, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Paying for nothing? (Cintas)., Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Box: 2, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Pinault-Printemps-Redoute: Global Pillage., Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Pinault-Printemps-Redoute: Global Pillage., Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: Pinault-Printemps-Redoute: Global Pillage., Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Box: 2, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Political Action Guide., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Box: 2, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Product Catalog, Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Item 2: Product Catalog, Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Item 3: Product Catalog, Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Box: 2, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Proposed Resolutions & Amendments, First Constitutional Convention., 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Box: 2, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Proposed Resolutions Assigned to Committees, Second Constitutional Convention, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Item 2: Proposed Resolutions Assigned to Committees, Second Constitutional Convention, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Item 3: Proposed Resolutions Assigned to Committees, Second Constitutional Convention, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Box: 2, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the First Constitutional Convention., 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Box: 2, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings of the Second Constitutional Convention., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Box: 2, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Resoluciones adoptados por la Primera Convencion Constituyente., 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Box: 2, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Retirees Association, Publication (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Item 2: Retirees Association, Publication (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Item 3: Retirees Association, Publication (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Box: 2, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Safety & Health Checklist, Publication (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Box: 2, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Jack Sheinkman, 1927-2004., Publication (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Box: 2, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Shopping Guide: Where to Find "Made in New York" Retail Apparel., Publication (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Box: 2, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Silver Threads., 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Item 2: Silver Threads., 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 51)
    Notes: September, 2003.
- Box: 2, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Staff Development and Education Courses., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Box: 2, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Stewards' Handbook., Publication (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Box: 2, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Stop Sweatshops, Take on Corporate America, Work With UNITE!, Publication (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Item 2: Stop Sweatshops, Take on Corporate America, Work With UNITE!, Publication (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Item 3: Stop Sweatshops, Take on Corporate America, Work With UNITE!, Publication (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Box: 2, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Stop the Pain! A Workers' Guide to Job Design., 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Item 2: Stop the Pain! A Workers' Guide to Job Design., 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Box: 2, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Sweatshop Holiday Catalog 2002/Brylane., Publication (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Item 2: Sweatshop Holiday Catalog 2002/Brylane., Publication (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Item 3: Sweatshop Holiday Catalog 2002/Brylane., Publication (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Box: 2, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: A Tribute to Sol Hoffman., 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Item 2: A Tribute to Sol Hoffman., 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Item 3: A Tribute to Sol Hoffman., 1999; Publication (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Box: 2, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Turning Dreams into Nighmares: Contributions for Clients?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Box: 2, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Union Predicts Company Tricks: Will The Be Right or Wrong? You Keep Score., Publication (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Item 2: Union Predicts Company Tricks: Will The Be Right or Wrong? You Keep Score., Publication (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Item 3: Union Predicts Company Tricks: Will The Be Right or Wrong? You Keep Score., Publication (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Box: 2, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: A Union at DDI Means Safe Staffing, Fairness and Peace of Mind., Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Item 2: A Union at DDI Means Safe Staffing, Fairness and Peace of Mind., Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Item 3: A Union at DDI Means Safe Staffing, Fairness and Peace of Mind., Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Box: 2, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: UNITE HERE merger media coverage., 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Box: 2, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: UNITE in the New Millenium: Celebrating Our Lives in Canada., 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 62)
    Author: Jonathan Eaton
- Box: 2, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: U.S Postal Sevice: Stamping Out Good Jobs., Publication (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Box: 2, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Want to make more money? Want more control over your job? Want to make a difference?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 2: Want to make more money? Want more control over your job? Want to make a difference?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 3: Want to make more money? Want more control over your job? Want to make a difference?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Box: 2, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: We Can Stop the Pain: OSHA's new standard would prevent stress and strain injuries., Publication (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Item 2: We Can Stop the Pain: OSHA's new standard would prevent stress and strain injuries., Publication (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Item 3: Podemos Poner un Alto al Dolor: Las Nuevas Normas de la OSHA evitarian Lesiones por Tension y Torceduras., Publication (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Item 4: Podemos Poner un Alto al Dolor: Las Nuevas Normas de la OSHA evitarian Lesiones por Tension y Torceduras., Publication (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Box: 2, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Withdrawl Card, Publication (Box 2, Folder 66)
    Notes: Three copies.
- Box: 2, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Worker Education Program: Shop Talk, 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 67)
    Author: Worker Education Program, UNITE.
    Notes: February 1996.
  - Item 2: Worker Education Program: Shop Talk, 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 67)
    Notes: February 1996. Copy 2.
- Box: 2, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Worker Education Program, UNITE., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 68)
    Notes: March 1996.
  - Item 2: Worker Education Program, UNITE., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 68)
    Notes: March 1996. Copy 2.
- Box: 2, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Worker Education Program: New Steps of the Union, UNITE., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 69)
    Notes: April 1996.
- Box: 2, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Worker Education Program: New Steps of the Union, UNITE., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 70)
    Notes: June 1996.
  - Item 2: Worker Education Program: New Steps of the Union, UNITE., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 70)
    Notes: June 1996. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Worker Education Program: New Steps of the Union, UNITE., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 70)
    Notes: June 1996. Copy 3.
- Box: 2, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Worker Education Program: New Steps of the Union, UNITE., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Notes: Summer 1996.
  - Item 2: Worker Education Program: New Steps of the Union, UNITE., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Notes: Summer 1996. Copy 2.
- Box: 2, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)